hbl.com 2013-03-01

# HBL

This Website is owned and controlled by Habib Bank Ltd. ("HBL"). HBL respects the privacy of visitors/surfers to its Website and advises all visitors/surfers and clients to read and understand our privacy policy, and to check it periodically for any updates or revisions.

When you visit this Website, HBL may collect personal data about you, either directly (where you are asked to provide the data). HBL will, however, only use such personal data for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement and HBL is committed to safeguarding such personal data. This statement sets out the purposes of HBL's data processing in respect of this Website.

HBL may gather and analyse information regarding usage of this Website, including domain name, the number of hits, the pages visited, previous/subsequent sites visited and length of user session.

**Purposes of Processing**  
HBL collects and processes information about customers and visitors to its Website to conduct its business, to inform and make available products and services that may be of interest to you and for the development of web statistics. The information provided by you can be used to contact you when necessary, e.g. to notify you about functionality changes to the web site and to offer services that you may find helpful (provided you have not opted out of receiving such services).

**Sensitive Data/Information**  
HBL does not seek to collect sensitive personal information (such as information revealing political opinions, religious beliefs, health or other matters) through this Website. If HBL does seek to collect such data, your prior consent thereto will be sought. Please note that, by providing HBL with unsolicited sensitive personal information you consent to our using such personal information as described hereinabove.

**Disclosure of Information**  
HBL may disclose information that it has collected from users to affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who may use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected in connection with a sale of our product and services.

**Third Party Sites**  
Please note that this Privacy Statement does not extend to third party websites linked to this Website.

**Amendments**  
HBL reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement or any part thereof at any time and from time to time. Please check this statement from time to time for any changes.
